Hello friends, I am Prem Arora Singh
Ajmera, present with the fair of Pandit,
today's first question is
on your screen, just now this is your
first question, you are a two-wheeler, the President
of Spain, and you know the road to right, you will, what will you be
for two-wheelers
after wearing helmets, and they will not be
withdrawn, it's time for love and you have to subscribe
and
on dad number, friends, as I told you earlier,
you must answer on Twitter,
but now go to our Laar Impress website,
its official website, and
register your responsibility, because if you want to
become a lucky winner, your answer is correct, and if
you want to include your name among those three lucky winners, then for that, first of all
you have to go to
our Indiagames and Brest website, the
link given there, and
submit your answer there, along with your
name and address, and share it with your mobile number,
if your name is included in our
automatic search, in which the names of lucky winners are
searched, then
our team can contact you, I
told my friends to participate enthusiastically, I asked the
question  Repeat second and you two wheeler
when unprecedented top speed you know the road
to right from your home what kind of two wheeler is there in it
very good so now you
can drive at that speed and if you
want to try it on the road also then what can you do so
your first answer here is that if you
go at night then will you find the road rough at night
Bhushan answer is that you will
drive your high speed vehicle in the middle of whatever vehicle is there because you think that is okay so
you people will wear green chillies and others
behind them and then you will
drive your vehicle at high speed Delhi is that
you will not do this at all because it can be
dangerous so friends whatever you
feel right stress on that and
your answer was register on our website
now I
am a flood so as we will talk to you more tomorrow
Tomar
challenge is going on to reduce road accidents Speed ​​Talent you should be
following it continuously our lady
driver has also shown you by driving 19 that
if you want to move in progress then you
You can drive,
you can explain this to your friends, your relatives, your family members that
we should drive safely, so
friends, to be safe,
even if we learn Arab, there are some
legal aspects in it, one is our own
personal responsibility, so first of all let
me explain to you the
legal aspects, the speed limit and
you must have seen on the road, it is said that the
mark of a circle is made of iron filings, in
it there is a click and Prakash Bhatt and
Soni and Bediya, many times it happens that there is a
picture made in the hair, that number and
a number is written with it, like it is
with the car and with the bike, there is
Prakash with Chalisa school, so friends, the
limits are of that vehicle on that road, the
maximum
speed limit of all the vehicles which is legally valid in
minutes, is made through the police and
administration only on that particular
road, on that particular road, whether it is a
highway, or an urban road, bridge road, you can also be careful against
vehicles exceeding that speed limit,
if you are
driving at a speed higher than that limit  If you drive, then the
administration and police can
crack down on you, they can make you thin,
you can be fined and then you can be suspended. There is an
honorable Supreme Court committee on this as per their
instructions but friends, what it
means is that if they fix a maximum speed limit for you, then
you should drive at that speed limit. It is
fine for you in India
but for other scenarios and insecurities, it is
necessary to have a safe speed limit as well because every person's driving
experience and expertise
and the way he
can handle his vehicle in different conditions is different.
So, as we are saying, speed limit is fixed for
any road, it is fixed keeping in mind all types
of vehicles and the experiences of the drivers. It is
fixed there in a blur
that you cannot drive on it,
but it is not said to you that you have to
drive at a certain speed limit. Friends, now even on the
safe speed limit, there is an
internal speed limit which is given to you as a maximum,
but after that what is our own safety speed
limit. Write the photo dignity of literature,
you cannot fix it with that, then that  It
can never be your personal because
if I have already
decided that you should drive only on the face then you will be
issued a challan and your license may be cancelled and it is
possible that
you may not be able to drive again and your
license may be cancelled if the
department officials drive you with that then
friends, in this we have to talk about the same thing again, at
least the mother of the victim
and the state are putting insecurity in it through proper means, when you drive on
any road, you should increase your
stress on that maximum speed limit,
if the speed limit falls on our land, then a
maximum speed
limit of the type has been fixed for them and on the national highway,
this meter is from the Government of India, so that is the
maximum speed limit which makes it fun that on this
national highway, if I am going in
my car, in a private vehicle,
not in a taxi, I am talking
due to private medical and if I am
taking it then I
can drive up to 100 kilometers per hour, friends, Arun,
but there is easy work in the wires, I
can handle it, even then if any danger
suddenly comes in front of me  If an animal comes, a
child passes, a person comes, a pothole comes
or any other vehicle breaks down and I
apply brakes, then can I
control my vehicle safely and
stop it without hitting it? If I can do so,
then it keeps me safe and
if I am not able to do so and I am driving at that speed, which can be as per a
human being in
kilometer per hour,
but my mental and physical condition
is such and I am driving the vehicle in this condition and in
that condition, if suddenly any
obstacle comes in front of me, any
kind of obstacle, I have to
handle it by applying brakes, then if I am not able to handle it at that speed limit
and
I am putting my own life in danger
or because of me I am
putting the life of that person in danger, then that
cannot be my safe speed limit, then if
I think carefully then
my safe limit is that
in any such obstacle, I keep my vehicle at
minimum damage without hitting anyone.
If I am able to control my weight and stop it while the power of life increases, if I am
walking with a smile, then it means that
I am driving at a safe speed, at a safe
distance and I can reverse my vehicle without causing any harm to anyone,
neither myself nor anyone else,
its control is in my hands,
so friends, if I
tell you my own example, then I have driven my vehicle many times
on the highway and even for 5 kilometers,
I have checked my vehicle in a moment, if you
cannot handle it, then friends,
I can handle it, I have no harm
in arguing that I can
only drive at the maximum set kilometer
per hour, only on the national highway where there are
wide roads and I get a layer to
bring property, even there I
cannot drive faster than the set meter per hour, the maximum that
gives me safety, the
maximum is soft, that is the only option,
if I am in the city limits, then I
cannot drive even at 60, so
friends, this protects me as per my own understanding,
which  I have determined this speed by driving it several times
and I realised that
I can still handle this speed of 7 kmph
in one go, I can stop it, as soon as the
fuel runs out I
cannot control my vehicle, so this is my
own progress on which I drive, so
friends, in the same way your own
progress in the Jhal keeps changing daily, in the
evening when we are coming back, we will
work the whole day, we have
Sattu and after that when we
drive out and reach our home, then at that
time our limit will be our manual, which is Harish's yesterday,
our agility, which we
control, then we will reach the higher
speed limit, the second one which we went in the morning, may
also be more for us in the evening, at
that time it is possible that in the evening
we will
not even set a record at 7 kmph, we may have to
drive at a speed less than that, so friends, that is why your
pair feels that the speed limit is the limit, it also
changes according to your experience and your own
physical condition, what is the condition of your body,
how is your mental state
and
It keeps
changing according to how much you have driven and how you are driving, so friends, you will have to decide this
and you will have to drive accordingly, so
friends, today I
told you a little bit about
how we can drive at a safe speed and we should take
advantage of the maximum speed limit and we should not suffer any loss,
we should take care of this and today I have asked
you a question,
this question is going on for 2 hours now, you can answer it
and the one is coming on your skin,
this is a two wheeler which has unlimited top
speed and you know the road to ride, but you will do a go ahead,
internet as soon as the road will be easy
for it, and two wheeler horns and
head after wearing helmets if these test
services decided not to withdraw, this
program was considered as a law, but their
slogan is protect your family with these
number and digital TV, this is tube white
people's search operation meghdoot amazon time
table of nation mithila box on the road
tempo spinal cord india then you
heard me about  Thank you very much for this,
I have just clarified to you through Abhinav Arora that
if I give Jai Hind to Jai
Ajay